# **DAMIAN MAART**

#### **DETAILS**

PHONE

0818718261

**EMAIL** 

damian.maart@gmail.com

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

1996/02/11 Robertson

**DRIVING LICENSE** 

В

NATIONALITY

South African

LINKS

<u>LinkedIn</u>

SKILLS

Computer Skills

• • • •

Communication

• • • •

Time Management

• • • • •

Leadership

• • • •

LANGUAGES

English

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$ 

Afrikaans

• • • •

#### PROFILE

A dedicated scholar with a Bachelor of Arts in Politics, Philosophy, and Economics (PPE) from the University of South Africa, currently pursuing Honours in Economics at the University of Cape Town. For my research I am looking into what economic and market factors influence the premiumisation of beer across different markets. Possessing a meticulous attention to detail, a passion for problem-solving, and a knack for strategic thinking, I bring valuable personal traits to any project or team dynamic.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

# Merchandiser, SGRP Meridian

Robertson

Mar 2023 — Jan 2024

### Merchandiser, Trilink Dynamics

Robertson

Dec 2019 — Feb 2023

### Waiter, Minnesota Spur

Mossel Bay

Nov 2018 — Jun 2019

### **Assistant**, Stockwell Primary

Ashton

Jan 2018 — Jul 2018

# **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelors of Commerce Honours in Economics, University of Cape Town**

Cape Town

Jan 2024 — Present

# Bachelor's of Arts in Politics, Philosophy, and Economics, University of South Africa

Pretoria

Jul 2019 — Oct 2023

Graduated with Distintion

# Bachelor's of Arts (General), University of Stellenbosch

Stellenbosch

Feb 2016 — Nov 2018

Not complete.

### **National Senior Certificate**, Robertson High

Roberson

Jan 2014 — Nov 2014

### REFERENCES

## References available upon request